<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R visualization on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</title>
    <link>/categories/r-visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R visualization on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r-visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cases in all of Germany</title>
      <link>/post/germanyallcases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germanyallcases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2021-03-25.
Data source: Our World In Data
December 2, 2020: Our World In Data originally obtained their data from ECDC. They have since switched data source to John Hopkins, and the daily numbers looked different from ECDC/RKI, due to different ways of updating their data. Therefore I have switched data source to RKI which seems to be the primary source for ECDC.
Cumulative number of confirmed SARS-CoV-2 cases in Germany in linear scale since March 15, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking the coronavirus outbreak in Germany from March 2020</title>
      <link>/post/germanycases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germanycases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2021-03-25.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from the Robert Koch Institute. Data used from March 15, 2020 (not updated every day).
For more extensive information about SARS-CoV-2 in Germany in English, see here.
 
Cumulative number of confirmed SARS-CoV-2 cases in Germany in linear scale since 100th case</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Coronavirus Cases in the World</title>
      <link>/post/worldcases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/worldcases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-04-14.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from ECDC. Data used from December 31, 2019-April 14, 2020 (not updated every day).
 
Doubling time for new cases and deaths I chose 10 countries to compare the rates of increase (in terms of doubling time) for the number of cases and the number of deaths, similar to the [NYT case growth rate visualization].</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>