<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Coronavirus SARS-CoV-2 pandemic-related links Johns Hopkins Coronavirus Resource Center: Latest data and news on the coronavirus outbreak, with dashboards and many useful data visualizations.
ECDC: European Center for Disease Prevention and Control, which has pretty good updated data and visualizations for the coronavirus outbreak.
WHO page for coronavirus pandemic: The official numbers from WHO. Their numbers tend to be a bit behind Johns Hopkins and ECDC though.
Our World in Data: Clean data visualization and statistics about the coronavirus pandemic in the world, including number of cases, amount of testing performed in each country, number of deaths, mortality rates, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a bioinformatician who is totally nerdy about data visualization, and studying data trends. Also a foodie, climber, and yogi. I am using the coronavirus quarantine period to teach myself to make a website, visualize coronavirus data, and machine learning / AI stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cases in all of Germany</title>
      <link>/post/germanyallcases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germanyallcases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-11-11.
Cumulative number of confirmed SARS-CoV-2 cases in Germany in linear scale since March 15, 2020  
 Number of confirmed new cases in Germany since March 15, 2020 This plot shows the increase in the number of confirmed new cases. Each data point is averaged over 7 previous consecutive days . Note: This is not necessarily reflective in the increase of actual number of cases each day, since the number of tests for the virus has been increasing as the pandemic progressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking the coronavirus outbreak in Germany from March 2020</title>
      <link>/post/germanycases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germanycases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-11-11.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from the Robert Koch Institute. Data used from March 15, 2020 (not updated every day).
For more extensive information about SARS-CoV-2 in Germany in English, see here.
 
Cumulative number of confirmed SARS-CoV-2 cases in Germany in linear scale since 100th case</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 development in May</title>
      <link>/post/coronavirusmay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/coronavirusmay/</guid>
      <description>Questions regarding coronavirus It has been nearly 2 months since I started this website. I have been mostly staying at home, applying for jobs, and following the coronavirus pandemic development pretty closely. As of May 14, many countries in Europe have started to ease the lockdown measures. Countries with a lot of cases, such as Spain, Italy, France, Belgium etc. have since large drops in numbers of new cases and deaths per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Coronavirus Cases in the World</title>
      <link>/post/worldcases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/worldcases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-04-14.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from ECDC. Data used from December 31, 2019-April 14, 2020 (not updated every day).
 
Doubling time for new cases and deaths I chose 10 countries to compare the rates of increase (in terms of doubling time) for the number of cases and the number of deaths, similar to the [NYT case growth rate visualization].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post of the site</title>
      <link>/post/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>First Post Hello World! I have always wanted to learn make a webpage, but lacked time, focus, and interesting contents to place on the website. I am currently searching for employement, but due to the coronavirus SARS-Cov-2 outbreak, both the economy and I are undergoing a lockdown right now. What better time than now to teach myself some skills that will make me more employable when pandemic become under control and the economy goes into recovery!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>