<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Coronavirus Cabin Fever</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 18:00:00 -0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Coronavirus Cases in the World</title>
      <link>/post/worldcases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 18:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/worldcases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-04-14.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from ECDC. Data used from December 31, 2019-April 14, 2020 (not updated every day).
 
Doubling time for new cases and deaths I chose 10 countries to compare the rates of increase (in terms of doubling time) for the number of cases and the number of deaths, similar to the [NYT case growth rate visualization].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Snapshot of the coronavirus outbreak in Germany in April 2020</title>
      <link>/post/germanycases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germanycases/</guid>
      <description>Last modified: 2020-05-06.
Note: added Saarland data on April 11 as its cases and deaths are rising quite fast while the numbers in many other states are stabilizing.
This is my attempt to visualize some SARS-CoV-2 data with some R code (please pardon the non-optimal layout). German data is obtained from the Robert Koch Institute. Data used from March 15-April 7, 2020 (not updated every day).
For more extensive information about SARS-CoV-2 in Germany in English, see here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post of the site</title>
      <link>/post/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>First Post Hello World! I have always wanted to learn make a webpage, but lacked time, focus, and interesting contents to place on the website. I am currently searching for employement, but due to the coronavirus SARS-Cov-2 outbreak, both the economy and I are undergoing a lockdown right now. What better time than now to teach myself some skills that will make me more employable when pandemic become under control and the economy goes into recovery!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>